

mark.nolledo@gmail.com

+63 905 399 9038



Noveleta, Cavite Philippines 4105

ABOUT

A Computer Science degree holder that has the skills and experience of a web programmer and a people-oriented service crew. Armed with technical and interpersonal skills, I could work well with any team and take on a variety of tasks.

SKILLS

Web Programming

Frontend development

- Node.JS, Webpack usage and configurations
- JavaScript frameworks such as Angular Vue for progressive web app development
- Ionic Framework 3 and 5 for cross-platform mobile apps
- Incorporation of CSS frameworks, UI and design toolkits
- API integration in frontend pages

Backend development

- Laravel and Lumen for PHP-based API development
- Django for Python-based API development
- Express for JavaScript-based API development
- Sequelize, Eloquent ORMs
- ERD design, normalization, query composition
- API testing tools such as Postman

Project Deployment and Maintenance

- Docker installation and configuration
- Shared server setup via YAMLs and Git postreceives
- Kubernetes pods deployment and configuration
- Usage of FTP and SSH for remote server access

Information Technology, Clerical, and Multimedia

- Microsoft Office and Google Suite
- Remote access tools such as TeamViewer
- Remote meeting tools such as Google Meet, Zoom
- IM platforms such as Discord, Slack, Teams
- Adobe Illustrator, Photoshop, InDesign
- Figma and Adobe XD for prototyping
- Basic network security protocols

EVENTS

February 6, 2019

HackForGov: CERT-PH Cyber Security Challenge **Department of Information and Communications** Technology (DICT)

Team finalist, national; an intercollegiate cybersecurity challenge held by the DICT and CERT-PH

February 23, 2019 - February 24, 2019

Bluehacks 2019 Ateneo de Manila University

Team participant; an intercollegiate hackathon organized by AdMU with the goal of designing a self-care game.

EDUCATION

Graduate, 2014 - 2019

Bachelor of Science in Computer Science Cavite State University - CCAT Campus

- Club Head, Programming Club
- Worked with SM Rosario for a joint project through the campus administration and college department
- Participated in an interuniversity and a national competition for college students
- Former layout artist for school publication

Undergraduate, 2011 - 2012

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology Adamson University

EXPERIENCE

Web Programmer, May 2022 - April 2024

Ole Elite Software Philippines, Inc. Rosario, Cavite, Philippines

Involved with the development, maintenance, and deployment of web applications, development and integration of REST APIs, and server configurations.

Part-time College Instructor, February 2022 - June 2024

Cavite State University - CCAT Campus Rosario, Cavite, Philippines

Teaches Computer Science subjects, tasked with technical critic advisory duties for thesis groups, and provides assistance to students through consultations.

Web Programmer, January 2021 - April 2022

Dynamic Markups IT Solutions Inc. Rosario, Cavite, Philippines

Helpdesk Technician I, July 2020 - November 2020

Stefanini Philippines Inc. Pasay, Metro Manila, Philippines

Junior Software Engineer, June 2019 - May 2020

LEENTech Network Solutions, Inc. Tanza, Cavite, Philippines

CERTIFICATIONS

March 2019

Civil Service Eligible - Professional Civil Service Commission - Philippines

> Piqued your interest? Let's connect.

